Division of Paleobotany Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
- Maps, Series I
  - Topographic Maps. United States., 000003
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Douglas East scale: 1: 24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4745-W10122.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000293
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Elgin scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4622.5-W10145/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000300
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Rice Lake scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4800-W10130/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000301
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Raleigh scale: 1: 24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4615-W10115/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000303
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Green Ridge scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4637.5-W10115/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000320
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Lake Tschida scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4630-W10145/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000341
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Lark scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4622.5-W10122.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000358
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Lake Vernon scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4752.5-W10130-7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000367
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Lake Tschida Eat scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4630-W10145/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000368
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Lake Tsichida W scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4630-W10152.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000369
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Makoti scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4752.5-W10145/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000374
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Max scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4745-W10115/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000376
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Mc Kenna Lake North scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4630-W9945/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000383
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Mork Lake scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4807.5-W10130/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000387
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Carson scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4622.5-W10130/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000395
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Minot SW scale: 1:24000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4800-W10122.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000411
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: The Hoback scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4630-W10045/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000418
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Nygren Dam scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4630-W10107.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000429
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Otter Creek E scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4630-W10115/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000431
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Otter Creek W scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4630-W10122.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000432
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Plaza scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4800-W10152.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000439
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Plaza NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4807.5-W10145/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000440
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Plaza SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4800-W10145/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000442
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: New Leipzig North scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4622.85-W10152.5/7.58 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000448
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Almont East scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4637.5-10122.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000457
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Almont West scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4637.5-W10130/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000458
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Breien scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4622.5-W10052.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000464
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Burgess scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4622.5-W10100/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000465
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Aurelia scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4822.5-W10152.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000471
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Bell Coulee East scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4607.5-W10115/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000489
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Bell Coulee W scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4607.5-W101022.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000490
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Berthold scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4815-W10137.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000497
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Saint Anthony scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4630-W10052.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000504
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Rush Lake scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4752.5-W10122.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000505
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Rohrich Dam scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4615-W10000/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000511
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Rice Lake scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4807-W10137.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000513
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: South Prairie scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4800-W10115/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000531
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Solen scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4622.5-W10045/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000536
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Heil scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4622.5-W10137.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000544
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Tagus scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4815-W10152.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000549
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Tagus SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4815-W10145/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000550
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Belfield scale: 1:100 00 Latitude/Longtitude: N4630-W10400/30*60 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000614
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Garrison scale: 1: 24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4737.5-W10122.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1981; 000264
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Garrison NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4737.5-W10115/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1981; 000267
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Coleharbor NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4737.5-W10100/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1981; 000278
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Coleharbor NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4737.5-W10107.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1981; 000279
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Kongsberg scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4745-W10045/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1981; 000347
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Long Lake scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4737.5-W10045/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1981; 000373
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Plaza NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4807.5-W10152.5/7.85 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1981; 000441
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Alkali Lake scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4737.5-W10037.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1981; 000454
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Burlington scale: 1:625000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4815-w10115/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1981; 000466
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Blacktail Coulee scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4752.5-W10052.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1981; 000473
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Benedict scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4745-W10100/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1981; 000492
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Benedict NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N47452.5-W10107.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1981; 000493
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Benedict SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4745-W10107.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1981; 000494
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Ryder scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4752.5-W10137.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1981; 000503
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Ruso scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4745-W10052.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1981; 000506
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Robinson Coulee scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4752.5-W10100/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1981; 000512
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Siebold Lake scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4737.5-W10030/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1981; 000540
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Horseshoe Valley scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4737.5-W10052/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1981; 000543
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Kulm scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4615-W9852.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1982; 000343
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: May Lake scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4607.5-W9930/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1982; 000379
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: May Lake NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4607.5-W9937.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1982; 000380
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: May Lake SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4600-W9930/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1982; 000381
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: May Lake SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4600-W9937.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1982; 000382
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Ashley East scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4600-W9915/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1982; 000468
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Ashley NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4607.5-W9915/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1982; 000469
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Ashley W scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4600-W9922.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1982; 000470
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Alkaline Lake scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4637.5-W9937.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1983; 000455
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Alkaline Lake SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4630-W9937.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1983; 000456
    - North Dakota. Quadrangle: Grassy Butte scale: 1:100 00 Latitude/Longtitude: N4700-W10400/30*60 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1983; 000613
    - North Dakota`. Quadrangle: scale: 1:150 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N/A Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1927; 000627
    - Utah-Wyoming. Quadrangle: Gilbert Peak scale: 1:125 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4030-W11000/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1908; 000628
    - Virginia. Quadrangle: Bermuda Hundred scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N3715-W7715/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1946; 000632
    - Virginia. Quadrangle: Annandale scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N3845-W7707.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1965; 000629
    - Virginia. Quadrangle: Hopewell scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N3715-W7715/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1969; 000630
    - Virginia. Quadrangle: Chester scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N3715-W7722.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1969; 000631
    - Washington. Quadrangle: Yakima scale: 1:250 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4600-W12000//100*200 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1948; 000633
    - Wyoming- Montana. Quadrangle: Clark scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4445-W10900/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1950; 000746
    - Wyoming- Montana. Quadrangle: Monarch scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4452.5-W10700/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1964; 000745
    - Wyoming- Montana. Quadrangle: Acme scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4452.5-W10652.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1968; 000747
    - Wyoming- Montana. Quadrangle: Bar N Draw scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4452.5-W10645/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1968; 000748
    - Wyoming- Montana. Quadrangle: Cedar Canyon scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4452.5-W106537.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1970; 000749
    - Wyoming- Montana. Quadrangle: Cody scale: 1:100 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4430-W11000/30*60 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000751
    - Wyoming- Montana. Quadrangle: Cody scale: 1:100 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4430-W11000/30*60 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000752
    - Wyoming- Montana. Quadrangle: Powell scale: 1:100 00 Latitude/Longtitude: N4430-W10900/30*60 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000755
    - Wyoming- Montana. Quadrangle: Powell scale: 1:100 00 Latitude/Longtitude: N4430-W10900/30*60 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1980; 000756
    - Wyoming- Montana. Quadrangle: Badger Basin scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N445230-W10900/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1987; 000750
    - Wyoming- Montana. Quadrangle: Bridger scale: 1:100 00 Latitude/Longtitude: N4500-W10900/30*60 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1989; 000754
    - Wyoming- Montana. Quadrangle: Bridger scale: 1:100 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4500-W10900/30*60 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1990; 000753
    - Wyoming-Montana. Quadrangle: Clark scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4445-W10900/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1950; 000758
    - Wyoming-Montana. Quadrangle: Clark scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N445-W10900/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1950; 000760
    - Wyoming-Montana. Quadrangle: Cowley scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4452.5-W10822.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000759
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Kirwin scale: 1:125000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4340-W10900/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1906; 000735
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Fremont Peak scale: 1:125000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4300-W10930/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1909; 000736
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Meeteetse scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4400-W10845/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1911; 000725
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Grass Creek Basin scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4345-W10830/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1913; 000695
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Grass Creek Basin scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4345-W10830/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1915; 000737
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Blue Mesa scale: 1:625000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4345-W10815/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1916; 000724
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Kirby scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4345-W10800/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1945; 000693
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Grand Teton Natl Park scale: 1:625000 Latitude/Longtitude: N11035-W4405/30*20 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1945; 000743
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Grand Teton Natl Park scale: 1:625000 Latitude/Longtitude: N432615-W1102230/3845*3280 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1948; 000742
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Cody scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4430-W10900/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1949; 000738
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Wilson Spring scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4407.5-W10837.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1951; 000637
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Y U Bench NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4422.5-W10837.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1951; 000640
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Y U Bench NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4422.5-W10830/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1951; 000641
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Dutch Nick Flat scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4400-W10815/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1951; 000642
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Tatman Mountain scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4415-W10830/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1951; 000643
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Sucker Dam scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4407.5-W10815/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1951; 000644
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Sheets Flat scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4415-210837.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1951; 000646
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Schuster Flats scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4400-W10807.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1951; 000649
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Schuster Flats NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4407.5-W10800/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1951; 000650
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Schuster Flats NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4407.5-W10807.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1951; 000651
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Schuster Flats SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4400-W10800/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1951; 000652
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Sheep Mt. scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4415-W10822.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1951; 000654
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Otto scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4422.5-W10815/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1951; 000657
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Dutch Nick Flat NW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4407.5-W10822.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1951; 000670
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Dutch Nick Flat SW scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4400-W10822.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1951; 000671
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Burlington scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4422.5-W10822.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1951; 000672
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Dead Indian Hill scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4407.5-W10830/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1951; 000673
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Hillberry Rim scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4400-W10837.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1951; 000680
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Gillies Draw scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4400-W10830/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1951; 000684
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Wardel Reservoir scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4415-W10815/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1951; 000688
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Maverick Spring scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4322.5-W10852.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1951; 000727
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Soapy Dale Peak scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4352.5-W10852.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1956; 000647
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Adam Weiss Peak scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4352.5-W10845/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1956; 000669
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Sunshine Reservoir scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4400-W10900/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1957; 000692
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Irish Rock scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4400-W10915/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1957; 000694
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Devils Tooth scale: 1:62500 Latitude/Longtitude: N4415-W10900/15 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1957; 000739
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Manderson scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4415-W10752.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1960; 000659
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Manderson NE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4422.5-W101745/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1960; 000660
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Manderson SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4415-W10745/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1960; 000661
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Devils Kitchen scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4430-W10752.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1960; 000676
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Hyatt Ranch scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4415-W10730/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1960; 000679
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Wild Horse Flats scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4422.5-W10752.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1960; 000687
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Flitner Reservoir scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4415-W10737.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1960; 000690
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Antelope Reservoir scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4207.5-W10752.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1961; 000667
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Lovell Lakes scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4445-W10815/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1964; 000663
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Kane scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4445-W10807.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1964; 000675
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Beaver Creek hills scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4437.5-W10700/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1964; 000696
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Sheridan Pass scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4330-W11000/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1965; 000726
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Deaver Reservoir scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4452.5-W10837.5/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000634
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Greybull North scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4430-W10800/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000635
    - Wyoming. Quadrangle: Elk Basin SE scale: 1:24 000 Latitude/Longtitude: N4445-W10845/7.5 Publisher: US Dept of the Interior Geological Survey, 1966; 000636